rightbiz.com 2009-06-18

# RightBiz Article Directory and Newsletter

Privacy Policy

RightBiz Enterprises respects the privacy of all our visitors and we will never sell, barter, or rent your Personally Identifiable Information (your name, e-mail address, street address, telephone number) to any unauthorized third party. Period." 

* Privacy policy   
* How we gather information from users   
* How we use any information collected   
* How this information is secured   
* How you can opt out or opt in to any mailing lists   
* How you can get more information   
* Spam Policy   

### Privacy Policy

Part of conducting daily busines requires us to ask visitors for personal data when enrolling, placing an order, such as name and address, credit-card information, and e-mail address. We use this data only for the purpose of processing a request, order, or communicating with the customer on a status of an inquiry or order. We treat this customer information as private and confidential, and we will not disclose this information to other individuals or organizations unless required by law. We will not distribute customer information to be used in mailing lists, surveys, or any other purpose other than what is required to perform our services. We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our customers' personal data.   

### External Links and Advertisements

RightBiz.com expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers accessible through our site, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit to our site you may link to, or view as part of a frame on a rightbiz.com page, certain content that is actually created or hosted by a third party. Also, through rightbiz.com you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, Web sites, features, contests or sweepstakes offered by other parties. rightbiz.com is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policies of those third parties when providing information on a feature or page operated by a third party.

While on our site, our advertisers, promotional partners or other third parties may use cookies or other technology to attempt to identify some of your preferences or retrieve information about you. For example, some of our advertising is served by third parties and may include cookies that enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before. Other features available on our site may offer services operated by third parties and may use cookies or other technology to gather information. rightbiz.com does not control the use of this technology by third parties or the resulting information, and is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.

You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable Information on message boards or in chat areas, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of rightbiz.com and this policy. 

### How we gather information from users

How we collect and store information depends on the page you are visiting, the activities in which you elect to participate and the services provided. For example, you may be asked to provide information when you register for access to certain portions of our site or request certain features, such as newsletters or when you make a purchase. You may provide information when you participate in sweepstakes and contests, message boards and chat rooms, and other interactive areas of our site. 

Like most Web sites, rightbiz.com also collects information automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may be transparent to our visitors. For example, we may log the name of your Internet Service Provider or use cookie technology to recognize you and hold information from your visit. Among other things, the cookie may store your user name and password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each time you visit, or may control the number of times you encounter a particular advertisement while visiting our site. 

As we adopt additional technology, we may also gather information through other means. In certain cases, you can choose not to provide us with information, for example by setting your browser to refuse to accept cookies, but if you do you may be unable to access certain portions of the site or may be asked to re-enter your user name and password, and we may not be able to customize the site’s features according to your preferences. 

### How we use any information collected

Like other Web publishers, we collect information to enhance your visit and deliver more individualized content and advertising. We respect your privacy and do not share your information with anyone.

Aggregated Information (information that does not personally identify you) may be used in many ways. For example, we may combine information about your usage patterns with similar information obtained from other users to help enhance our site and services (e.g., to learn which pages are visited most or what features are most attractive). Aggregated Information may occasionally be shared with our advertisers and business partners. Again, this information does not include any Personally Identifiable Information about you or allow anyone to identify you individually.

We may use Personally Identifiable Information collected on rightbiz.com to communicate with you about your registration and customization preferences; our Terms of Service and privacy policy; services and products offered by rightbiz.com and other topics we think you might find of interest.

Personally Identifiable Information collected by rightbiz.com may also be used for other purposes, including but not limited to site administration, troubleshooting, processing of e-commerce transactions, administration of sweepstakes and contests, and other communications with you. Certain third parties who provide technical support for the operation of our site (our Web hosting service for example) may access such information. We will use your information only as permitted by law. In addition, from time to time as we continue to develop our business, we may sell, buy, merge or partner with other companies or businesses. In such transactions, user information may be among the transferred assets. We may also disclose your information in response to a court order, at other times when we believe we are reasonably required to do so by law, in connection with the collection of amounts you may owe to us, and/or to law enforcement authorities whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary. Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases. 

### How this information is secured

We store basic contact information of our opt-in mailing list members on two password protected computer hard drives.

We also store the contact details of our web based marketing members on password protected computer hard drives and on a password protected SQL database residing on a secure web server. 

### How you can opt out or opt in to any mailing lists

You can opt out of any auto-responder series of e-mails by following the instructions at the end of each e-mail.

You can also opt out of our mailing list by sending us an e-mail with your subscribed name and e-mail address, and the words "opt-out" in the subject line. Just send it to opt-out@rightbiz.com

You can subscribe to our mailing list by sending an e-mail with your name and e-mail address, with the words "opt-in" in the subject line. Just send it to opt-in@rightbiz.com 

### How you can get more information

Send an email to info@rightbiz.com stating what it is you want, or use our on-line form at the[ Helpdesk](http://www.rightbiz.com/cgi-bin/uss/login.cgi?login)

### Spam Policy

Spamming, such as indiscriminate advertising, unsolicited commercial email, or posting to off-topic USENET groups, is perceived by the vast majority of netizens as unprofessional, second rate and an utter nuisance. Therefore, RightBiz Enterprises has formed a strict policy against spamming of any description and none will be tolerated. 

### Changes to this Policy

RightBiz.com reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected.  |  [](http://www.twitter.com/rightbiz)
